I killed Sirius Black!
내가 시리우스 블랙을
죽였다!
He's back.
'그'가 돌아왔소
The police are
continuing with the investigation...
... into the cause
of the Millennium Bridge disaster.
Traffic has been halted
as police search for survivors.
해리 포터
선택받은 자?
경찰은
생존자 수색 중에 있으며
The surrounding area remains closed.
주변 지역은
봉쇄돼 있습니다
The mayor has urged Londoners
to remain calm...
시장은 런던 시민들이
침착하게…
말포이 가문의 몰락
"Harry Potter."
"해리 포터"
Who's Harry Potter?
걔가 누구야?
Oh, no one.
아무도 아냐
Bit of a tosser, really.
멍청한 애지
Funny, that paper of yours.
신문 속 사진이
Couple nights ago,
I could've sworn I saw a picture move.
살아 움직이는 거 같았어
- Really?
- Thought I was going around the twist.
- 진짜?
- 내가 잘못 봤겠지
- Hey, I was wondering...
- Eleven. That's when I get off.
- 혹시…
- 11시, 그때 끝나
You can tell me all about
that tosser Harry Potter.
해리 포터에 대해
다 말해 줘
You've been reckless this summer, Harry.
혼자 다니면 위험해
I like riding around on trains.
기차 타는 걸 좋아해요
Takes my mind off things.
고민도 잊혀지구요
Rather unpleasant to behold, isn't it?
보기 흉하지?
The tale is thrilling,
if I say so myself.
아주 흥미진진한 대결이었지
But now is not the time to tell it.
지금은 말해 줄
시간이 없구나
Take my arm.
내 팔 잡아
Do as I say.
어서
I just Apparated, didn't I?
순간 이동한 거죠?
Indeed. Quite successfully too,
I might add.
그래, 아주 멀쩡하구나
Most people vomit the first time.
처음엔 다들 토하는데
I can't imagine why.
전 다른가 보죠
Welcome to the
charming village of Budleigh Babberton.
버드레이 바베르톤
마을이다
Harry, I assume, right about now, you're
wondering why I brought you here.
여길 데려온 이유가
궁금할 거야
Am I right?
그렇지?
Actually, sir, after all these years,
I just sort of go with it.
이젠 이런 상황에
익숙한걸요
Wands out, Harry.
지팡이 꺼내
Horace?
호레이스?
선택받은 자?
Merlin's beard!
마법사 맙소사!
No need to disfigure me, Albus.
찌를 건 없잖아, 덤블도어
Well, I must say you
make a very convincing armchair, Horace.
진짜 의자 같았네, 호레이스
It's all in the upholstery. I come by the
stuffing naturally. What gave me away?
통통한 의자라 배 감추기 딱 좋지
어떻게 알았나?
Dragon's blood.
용의 피!
- Oh.
- Oh, yes, introductions.
참, 소개하지
Harry, I'd like you to meet
an old friend and colleague of mine...
해리, 내 동료이자
오랜 친구인
...Horace Slughorn.
호레이스 슬러그혼
Horace...
호레이스
...well, you know who this is.
얘가 누군지 알지?
Harry Potter.
해리 포터
What's with all the theatrics, Horace?
왜 숨어 있어?
You weren't, by any chance,
waiting for someone else?
누가 찾아올까 봐
두려웠나?
Someone else?
I'm sure I don't know what you mean.
무슨 소린지 모르겠구만
All right, the Death Eaters have been
trying to recruit me for over a year.
실은, 죽음을 먹는 자들
협조 요구를
Do you know what that's like?
거절했는데
You can only say no so many times, so
I never stay anywhere more than a week.
보복이 두려워서
계속 숨어 다녔어
Muggles who own this
are in the Canary Islands.
집주인은 여행을 갔지
Well, I think we should put it back
in order for them, don't you? Mind.
원래대로 해 놓자구
뒤로 좀
That was fun.
깔끔해졌군
- Do you mind if I use the loo?
- No, of course.
- 화장실 좀?
- 그래
Don't think I don't know
why you're here, Albus.
날 찾아온 이유 아는데
The answer's still no.
Absolutely and unequivocally, no.
난 싫어
진짜로 무조건 싫어
You're very like your father.
아빠를 빼닮았군
- Except for the eyes. You have your...
- My mother's eyes. Yeah.
- 하지만 눈은…
- 엄마를 닮았죠
Lily. Lovely Lily. She was
exceedingly bright, your mother.
릴리
참 예쁘고 똑똑했지
Even more impressive when one
considers she was Muggle-born.
머글 태생이란 게
놀라울 정도였어
One of my best friends is Muggle-born.
Best in our year.
제 친한 친구도 머글인걸요
Please don't think I'm prejudiced.
No, no.
오해하진 마라
Your mother was one of my
absolute favorites. Look, there she is.
내가 아낀 제자였는걸
봐라, 네 엄마다
Right at the front.
앞줄에
All mine. Each and every one.
모두 내 제자들이지
Ex-students, I mean.
옛날에 가르친…
You recognize Barnabas Cuffe,
editor of The Daily Prophet.
'예언자 일보' 편집장
바르나바스 커프
Always takes my owl,
should I wish to register an opinion...
항상 내 의견을
신문에 실어 주지
...on the news of the day.
Gwenog Jones,
captain of the Holyhead Harpies.
홀리헤드 하피스 팀
그웨녹 존스 주장
Free tickets whenever I want them.
공짜표를 줘
Of course, I haven't been
to a match in some time.
퀴디치 경기 본 지는
까마득하지만
Ah, yes.
그래
Regulus Black.
레귤러스 블랙
You no doubt know of his older brother
Sirius. Died a few weeks ago.
형이 얼마 전에 죽은
시리우스야
I taught the whole Black family,
except Sirius.
제자는 아니었지만
It's a shame. Talented boy.
인재였는데
안타까운 일이지
I got Regulus when he came along,
of course, but I'd have liked the set.
레귤러스처럼
내가 가르쳤으면 참 좋았을 텐데
Horace?
호레이스?
Do you mind if I take this?
가져가도 되겠나?
- I do love knitting patterns.
- Yes, of course. But you're not leaving?
- 뜨개질 패턴에 관심 많거든
- 그래, 벌써 가려구?
I think I know a lost cause
when I see one. Regrettable.
자네 결심이
확고한 거 같아서
I would have considered it
a personal triumph...
호그와트 교수직 복귀를
...had you consented to return
to Hogwarts. Oh, well.
수락해 줬으면
무척 기뻤겠지만!
You're like my friend Mr. Potter here,
one of a kind.
자넨 해리처럼 특별하잖나
Well, bye-bye, Horace.
그럼 가겠네
Bye.
잘 있게
All right. I'll do it.
좋아, 하겠어!
But I want Professor Merrythought's old
office, not the water closet I had before.
대신 메리쏘우트 교수가
쓰던 방 주고
And I expect a raise.
These are mad times we live in. Mad!
월급도 올려 줘
미친 세상이잖아!
They are indeed.
그래, 미친 세상이지
Sir, exactly what was all that about?
왜 절 데려온 거죠?
You are talented, famous and powerful.
Everything Horace values.
호레이스는
재능, 인기, 힘을 중시해
Professor Slughorn is gonna try
to collect you, Harry.
그 조건들을 갖춘 널 보면
You would be his crowning jewel.
제자로 삼을 걸 알았지
That's why he's returning to Hogwarts.
And it's crucial he should return.
그래서 교수직을 수락한 거야
호그와트엔 그가 필요해
I fear I may have stolen
a wondrous night from you, Harry.
기대하던 데이트
망쳐서 미안하다
She was, truthfully, very pretty, the girl.
참 예쁘더구나
그 식당 아가씨 말이야
It's all right, sir. I'll go back tomorrow,
make some excuse.
괜찮아요, 내일 잘 말할게요
Oh, you'll not be returning
to Little Whinging tonight, Harry.
집엔 못 간다, 해리
But, sir, what about Hedwig?
And my trunk?
그럼 헤드위그는?
제 짐은요?
Both are waiting for you.
벌써 손을 써 놨다
Hedwig.
헤드위그
Mum?
엄마?
Ginny, what is it?
지니, 왜?
I was only wondering
when Harry got here.
해리 언제 왔어요?
- What? Harry? Harry who?
- Harry Potter, of course.
- 뭐? 해리 누구?
- 해리 포터요
I think I'd know if Harry Potter
was in my house, wouldn't I?
해리가 왔으면
내가 몰랐겠니?
- His trunk's in the kitchen, and his owl.
- No, dear, I seriously doubt that.
- 주방에 가방이랑 부엉이가 있어요
- 설마, 잘못 봤겠지
해리가 왔다구?
Harry? Did someone say "Harry"?
Me, nosy. Is he up there with you?
오빠 방에 있어?
Of course not. I'd know if my best friend
was in my room, wouldn't I?
내 방에 있으면
내가 모르겠냐?
- Is that an owl?
- You haven't seen him, have you?
- 부엉이가 뭐?
- 언니도 몰라?
He's wandering about the house.
집 밖에 있나 봐
- Really?
- Really.
- 진짜?
- 진짜!
Harry!
해리!
Hello.
What a lovely surprise.
정말 뜻밖이구나
Why didn't you let us know
you were coming?
왜 온다고 연락 안 했어?
- I didn't know. Dumbledore.
- Oh, that man.
- 덤블도어 교수님이…
- 그 노친네!
But then, what would we do
without him?
그래도 좋은 분이지
Got a bit of toothpaste.
치약 묻었어
So when did you get here?
언제 왔어?
A few days ago.
며칠 전에
Though for a while,
I wasn't sure I was coming.
망설이다가 왔어
Mum sort of lost it last week.
엄마가 난리 쳤었어
Said Ginny and I had no business
going back to Hogwarts.
호그와트에
돌아가지 말라면서
That it's too dangerous.
너무 위험하다고
- Oh, come on.
- She's not alone.
- 말도 안 돼
- 아줌마만 그런 게 아냐
Even my parents, and they're Muggles,
know something bad's happening.
머글인 우리 부모님도
이상한 낌새 차리셨어
Anyway, Dad stepped in,
told her she was being barmy...
다행히 아빠가 잘 설득해서
...and it took a few days,
but she came around.
지금은 괜찮으셔
But this is Hogwarts we're talking about.
It's Dumbledore. What could be safer?
덤블도어가 있는데
뭐가 위험해?
There's been a lot of talk recently that...
사람들 말이
...Dumbledore's got a bit old.
교수님이 너무 늙었대
Rubbish! Well, he's only...
아냐, 이제 겨우…
What is he?
몇 살이시지?
Hundred and fifty?
Give or take a few years.
150살? 대충 그쯤일 거야
Cissy! You can't do this!
He can't be trusted!
씨시, 그를 믿으면 안 돼
The Dark Lord trusts him.
어둠의 마왕님은 그를 믿어
- The Dark Lord's mistaken.
- Pfft.
실수하시는 거야
Run along, Wormtail.
가 봐, 웜테일
I know I ought not to be here.
여기 오면
안 되는 줄 알아요
The Dark Lord himself
forbade me to speak of this.
어둠의 마왕께선
입을 다물라셨죠
If the Dark Lord has forbidden it,
you ought not to speak.
그럼 다물어야지요
Put it down, Bella.
We mustn't touch what isn't ours.
내려놔, 벨라트릭스
네 게 아니잖아
As it so happens,
I'm aware of your situation, Narcissa.
부인이 처한 상황은
알고 있소
You?
안다구?
The Dark Lord told you?
어둠의 마왕께서
말해 주셨어?
Your sister doubts me.
동생은 날 안 믿는군요
Understandable. Over the years
I've played my part well.
이해할 만해
내 연기가 뛰어났지
So well, I've deceived
one of the greatest wizards of all time.
위대한 마법사도
감쪽같이 속였으니
덤블도어는 위대한 마법사야
그건 의심할 여지가 없어
Dumbledore is a great wizard.
Only a fool would question it.
I don't doubt you, Severus.
난 당신을 믿어요
You should be honored, Cissy.
As should Draco.
그런 임무 맡은 건
드레이코한테 영광이야
He's just a boy.
걘 아직 어려요
I can't change the Dark Lord's mind.
난 마왕님 마음을
못 바꿉니다
But it might be possible
for me to help Draco.
허나 드레이코를
도와줄 순 있지요
- Severus.
- Swear to it.
- 스네이프
- 맹세를 해
Make the Unbreakable Vow.
깨뜨릴 수 없는 맹세를!
It's just empty words.
말만으론 안돼
He'll give it his best effort.
드레이코를 돕겠다 해 놓고
But when it matters most...
가장 중요한 순간에
...he'll just slither back into his hole.
등을 돌리고 말 거야
Coward.
겁쟁이처럼!
Take out your wand.
네 지팡이를 꺼내
Will you...
세베루스 스네이프
...Severus Snape...
...watch over Draco Malfoy...
당신은 드레이코 말포이가
...as he attempts to fulfill
the Dark Lord's wishes?
마왕님의 지시를
완수하게 돕겠는가?
I will.
그렇다
And will you,
to the best of your ability...
최선을 다해서
...protect him from harm?
그 아이의 목숨을
지켜 주고?
I will.
그렇다
And if Draco should fail...
만약 드레이코가 실패하면
...will you yourself carry out the deed...
녀석을 대신해서
...the Dark Lord
has ordered Draco to perform?
마왕님의 뜻을 완수하겠는가?
I will.
그렇다
Step up! Step up!
We've got Fainting Fancies!
골라, 골라!
기절 사탕!
Nosebleed Nougats!
코피 누가 사탕!
- And just in time for school...
- Puking Pastilles!
- 개학 맞이 바겐세일!
- 구역질 사탕!
- Into the cauldron, handsome.
이 통에 토해
I will have order!
모두 질서를 지켜!
I really hate children. I will have order!
- Peruvian Instant Darkness Powder.
- A real money spinner, that.
- 페루산 즉석 암흑 가루네
- 효자 상품이야
Handy if you need
to make a quick getaway.
도망칠 때 딱이지
- Hello, ladies.
안녕, 아가씨들
- Love potions, eh?
- Yeah, they really do work.
- 사랑의 묘약?
- 좋지, 효과 끝내줘
Then again, the way we hear it, sis,
you're doing just fine on your own.
그치만 넌 그런 거
필요 없잖아
Meaning?
- 무슨 뜻이야?
- 딘 토마스랑 사귄다며?
Are you not
currently dating Dean Thomas?
It's none of your business.
신경 끊어 줘
How much for this?
이거 얼마야?
- Five Galleons.
5갈레온
- How much for me?
- Five Galleons.
- 나한텐?
- 5갈레온
I'm your brother.
난 동생이잖아
- Ten Galleons.
10갈레온!
Come on, let's go.
가자
Hi, Ron.
안녕, 론
Hi.
안녕
How are Fred and George
doing it? Half the Alley's closed down.
너희 형들 대단해
다른 가게는 다 닫았는데
Fred reckons
people need a laugh these days.
이럴 때일수록
웃음이 필요하대
I reckon he's right.
맞는 말이야
Oh, no.
이런!
Everyone got their wands
from Ollivander's.
다 이 가게에서
지팡이를 샀었는데
Harry?
해리?
Is it me, or do Draco and Mummy
look like two people...
드레이코랑 엄마가
좀 수상하지 않아?
...who don't want to be followed?
Quibbler.
'이러쿵 저러쿵'?
He's lovely. They've been known
to sing on Boxing Day, you know.
너무 귀엽다
성탄절에 노래하는 새네
- Quibbler?
- Oh, please.
- '이러쿵 저러쿵'?
- 응
- What's a Wrackspurt?
- They're invisible creatures.
- '랙스퍼츠'가 뭐야?
- 투명 벌레
They float in your ears
and make your brain go fuzzy.
귓속에 들어가서
어지럽게 만들어
Quibbler.
'이러쿵 저러쿵'?
So, what was Draco doing
with that weird-looking cabinet?
그 이상하게 생긴
캐비닛은 뭐지?
And who were all those people?
그 사람들은 누구고?
Don't you see?
It was a ceremony, an initiation.
모르겠어?
의식을 치른 거야
Stop it, Harry.
I know where you're going.
그만해, 해리
아닐 거야
It's happened. He's one of them.
그들처럼 된 거야
One of what?
뭐?
Harry is under the impression
Draco Malfoy is now a Death Eater.
드레이코 말포이가
죽음을 먹는 자가 됐대
You're barking.
말도 안 돼
What would You-Know-Who
want with Malfoy?
어둠의 마왕이
말포이를 왜?
Well, then what's he doing in Borgin
and Burkes? Browsing for furniture?
아님 그 가게엔 왜?
가구 사러?
It's a creepy shop. He's a creepy bloke.
섬뜩한 가게야
말포이도 그렇고
Look, his father is a Death Eater.
It only makes sense.
걔 아버지도
죽음을 먹는 자잖아
Hermione saw it with her own eyes.
헤르미온느도 봤어
I told you, I don't know what I saw.
말했잖아
난 자세히 못 봤어
I need some air.
바람 쐬고 올게
Don't worry. When we get
to Hogwarts, we'll sort it out.
- What was that? Blaise?
- Don't know.
- 뭐야? 블레이즈?
- 몰라
Relax, boys. It's probably just
a first-year messing around.
아마 신입생들이
장난친 걸 거야
Come on, Draco. Sit down.
We'll be at Hogwarts soon.
앉아, 드레이코
곧 호그와트 도착해
Hogwarts.
What a pathetic excuse for a school.
호그와트는 쓰레기 학교야
I'd pitch myself off
the Astronomy Tower...
2년을 더 다녀야 한다면
...if I had to continue
for another two years.
탑에서 뛰어내렸을 거야
What's that supposed to mean?
무슨 소리야?
Let's just say you won't see me wasting
my time in Charms class next year.
내년엔 호그와트에서
수업 받을 일 없다구
Amused, Blaise?
웃겨?
We'll see just who's laughing in the end.
마지막에
누가 웃는지 보자구
You two go on.
I wanna check something.
먼저 가, 확인할 게 있어
Where's Harry?
해리는?
He's probably already on the platform.
Come on.
먼저 내렸겠지, 가자
Didn't Mummy ever tell you
it was rude to eavesdrop, Potter?
엿듣는 건 나쁘다고
엄마한테 못 배웠어?
Petrificus Totalus.
페트리피쿠스 토탈루스!
Oh, yeah...
참…
...she was dead before you could wipe
the drool off your chin.
엄마 얼굴도 모르고
자란 고아지
That's for my father.
Enjoy your ride back to London.
아버지의 복수다
런던으로 돌아가
Finite.
피니테!
- Hello, Harry.
- Luna!
- 안녕, 해리
- 루나
- How'd you know where I was?
- Wrackspurts. Your head's full of them.
- 날 어떻게 찾았어?
- 랙스퍼츠! 네 머리 위에 떠다녀
Sorry I made you miss
the carriages, by the way, Luna.
미안해
나 땜에 마차 놓쳤어
That's all right.
It was like being with a friend.
괜찮아
친구랑 있는 거 같았는걸
Oh, I am your friend, Luna.
우린 친구잖아
That's nice.
고마워
About time. I've been looking
all over for you two.
이제야!
둘을 한참 찾았어
Right. Names?
좋아, 이름?
Professor Flitwick,
you've known me for five years.
절 안 지 5년 됐잖아요
No exceptions, Potter.
예외는 없어, 포터
Who are those people?
누구죠?
Aurors. For security.
오러들
짐을 검사해
What's this cane here, then?
이 막대긴 뭐지?
It's not a cane, you cretin.
It's a walking stick.
막대기가 아니라
지팡이예요
And what exactly would you
be wanting with a...?
왜 지팡이를 갖고 다녀?
Could be construed
as an offensive weapon.
무기로 쓸 수 있잖아
It's all right, Mr. Filch.
I can vouch for Mr. Malfoy.
그건 걱정하지 말게
내가 책임지지
Nice face, Potter.
꼴 좋네, 포터
Would you like me to fix it for you?
내가 고쳐 줄까?
Personally, I think you look
a bit more devil-may-care this way...
지금 모습이
더 매력적이긴 하지만
...but it's up to you.
좋을 대로 해
Well, have you ever fixed a nose before?
부러진 코 고쳐 봤어?
No, but I've done several toes,
and how different are they, really?
아니, 발가락만…
다를 게 뭐 있겠어?
Um... Okay, yeah. Give it a go.
좋아, 해봐
- Episkey.
- Ah!
에피스키!
- How do I look?
- Exceptionally ordinary.
- 어때?
- 아주 정상이야
Brilliant.
다행이네
Don't worry. He'll be here in a minute.
걱정 마, 금방 올 거야
Will you stop eating?
그만 좀 먹어라!
Your best friend is missing!
친구가 사라졌잖아!
Oi. Turn around, you lunatic.
뒤를 봐, 이 편집증 환자야
He's covered in blood again.
또 피범벅이야
- Why is it he's always covered in blood?
- Looks like it's his own this time.
- 왜 항상 저럴까?
- 이번엔 자기 피야
Where have you been?
어디 갔었어?
- What happened to your face?
- Later.
- 얼굴은?
- 나중에!
What've I missed?
시작했어?
Sorting Hat urged us all to be brave
and strong in these troubled times.
분류 모자가
힘든 시기니 용감해지래
Easy for it to say, huh?
It's a hat, isn't it?
말은 쉽지
모자가 뭘 알겠어?
Very best of evenings to you all.
반갑습니다, 여러분
Thanks.
First off, let me introduce
the newest member of our staff...
먼저, 새 교수님을
소개하겠어요
...Horace Slughorn.
호레이스 슬러그혼
Professor Slughorn, I'm happy to say...
슬러그혼 교수님이
...has agreed to resume
his old post as Potions Master.
다시 마법약 수업을 맡아
참 기쁘군요
Meanwhile, the post of
Defense Against the Dark Arts...
그리고 어둠의 마법 방어술을
가르쳐 주실
...will be taken by Professor Snape.
스네이프 교수님
Snape?
Now, as you know...
여러분이
...each and every one of you was searched
upon your arrival here tonight.
도착하자마자 검색을 받은
And you have the right to know why.
이유를 말해 줄게요
Once there was a young man,
who, like you...
옛날에 한 학생도
여러분처럼
...sat in this very hall...
이 연회장에 앉고
...walked this castle's corridors,
slept under its roof.
복도를 걷고
기숙사에서 잤어요
He seemed to all the world
a student like any other.
다른 학생들하고
다를 게 없었지요
His name?
그 학생의 이름은
Tom Riddle.
톰 리들
Today, of course...
지금은
...he's known all over the world
by another name.
다른 이름으로
잘 알려져 있죠
Which is why, as I stand looking out
upon you all tonight...
이 자리를 빌어
여러분 모두에게
...I'm reminded of a sobering fact.
다시 강조합니다
Every day, every hour...
매일 매시간
...this very minute, perhaps...
지금 이 순간에도
...dark forces attempt to penetrate
this castle's walls.
어둠의 세력이
우리 학교를 노려요
But in the end,
their greatest weapon is you.
여러분을 자신들 무기로
삼기 위해서지요
Just something to think about.
잘 생각해 봐요
Now, off to bed. Pip-pip.
이제 잠자리로!
That was cheerful.
오싹하네
History of Magic is upstairs,
ladies, not down.
마법의 역사 반은
위층이에요!
Mr. Davies! Mr. Davies!
That is the girls' lavatory.
데이비스 군!
거긴 여자 화장실이야
Potter.
포터
Oh, this can't be good.
예감이 안 좋아
Enjoying ourselves, are we?
뭐 하고 있지?
- I had a free period this morning.
- So I noticed.
- 아침 수업이 없어요
- 그런 거 같구나
I would think you would want to
fill it with Potions.
마법약 수업
들을 줄 알았는데
Or is it no longer your ambition
to become an Auror?
오러가 될 꿈은 포기했나?
It was, but I was told I had to
get an "Outstanding" in my O.W.L.
OWL 점수가
높아야 한대서요
So you did, when Professor Snape
was teaching Potions.
스네이프 교수님
수업일 땐 그랬지
However, Professor Slughorn is perfectly
happy to accept N.E.W.T. s students...
슬러그혼 교수님은 기꺼이
평범한 점수 받은 학생도
...with "Exceeds Expectations."
받아 주실 거다
Brilliant. Um...
잘됐네요
- Well, I'll head there straightaway.
- Oh, good, good.
- 지금 갈게요
- 좋아
Potter, take Weasley with you.
He looks far too happy over there.
위즐리도 데려가
아주 좋아하는구나
I don't wanna take Potions.
마법약 수업 싫은데!
This is Quidditch trials coming up.
I need to practice.
퀴디치 선수 선발전
연습해야 돼
Attention to detail
in the preparation...
올바른 재료 준비가
가장 중요하다
...is the prerequisite of all planning.
Ah.
Harry, my boy, I was beginning to worry.
We've brought someone with us, I see.
해리, 걱정했다
친구도 데려왔구나
Ron Weasley, sir.
론 위즐리예요
But I'm dead awful at Potions,
a menace, actually.
전 마법약엔
아주 재주 없어요
- I'm gonna...
- Nonsense, we'll sort you out.
- 그러니까…
- 배우면 돼
Any friend of Harry's is a friend of mine.
Get your books out.
해리 친구라면
환영이다, 책 꺼내
I haven't actually got
my book yet, and nor has Ron.
죄송하지만
둘 다 책이 없어요
Get what you want from the cupboard.
걱정 마, 캐비닛에 있다
Now, as I was saying,
I prepared some concoctions this morning.
오늘 아침에 만든 건데
Any ideas what these might be?
무슨 약인지 맞춰 볼 사람?
- Yes, Miss...?
- Granger, sir.
- 이름이?
- 헤르미온느요
That one there is Veritaserum.
It's a truth-telling serum.
저건 베리타세룸
진실을 말하게 만드는 약이고
And that would be Polyjuice Potion.
저건 폴리 주스
마법약인데
It's terribly tricky to make.
만들기 까다롭죠
And this is Amortentia...
이건 암모텐시아
...the most powerful
love potion in the world.
강력한 사랑의 묘약인데
It's rumored to smell differently to each
person according to what attracts them.
끌리는 대상에 따라
냄새가 다르게 나죠
For example, I smell...
저한텐
...freshly mown grass,
and new parchment, and...
방금 막 깎은 잔디
새 양피지
...spearmint toothpaste.
박하향 치약 냄새가 나요
Amortentia doesn't create
actual love. That would be impossible.
진짜 사랑을
만들어 내진 않지만
But it does cause
a powerful infatuation or obsession.
사람을 홀리거나
집착하게 만든다
And for that reason, it is probably
the most dangerous potion in this room.
그래서 그 어떤
마법약보다 위험하지
Sir? You haven't told us
what's in that one.
교수님? 저 병에 든 건요?
Oh, yes.
그래
What you see before you,
ladies and gentlemen...
지금 여러분이
보고 있는 약은
...is a curious little potion
known as Felix Felicis.
아주 특별한 거다
이름은 펠릭스 펠리시스
But it is more commonly referred to as...
일반적으로
불리는 이름은…
- Liquid luck.
- Yes, Miss Granger. Liquid luck.
- 행운의 물약!
- 그래, 행운의 물약이지
Desperately tricky to make,
disastrous should you get it wrong.
만들기도 어렵고
잘못 만들면 역효과가 나
One sip and you will find
that all of your endeavors succeed.
한 모금만 마시면
노력하는 모든 걸 이루게 돼
At least until the effects wear off.
약효가 사라지기 전까지만!
So this is what I offer each of you today.
여러분한테 제안을 하겠다
One tiny vial of liquid luck to the student
who, in the hour that remains...
남은 시간 동안
살아 있는 죽음의 약을
...manages to brew an acceptable
Draught of Living Death...
제대로 만드는 학생에겐
이 약을 주지
...the recipes for which can be found
on page 10 of your books.
만드는 법은
10쪽에 나와 있다
I should point out, however, only once did
a student manage to brew a potion...
미리 말하지만
지금까지 약을 잘 만들어
...of sufficient quality to
claim this prize.
상 탄 사람은
단 한 명이야
Nevertheless, good luck to you all.
행운을 빈다
Let the brewing commence.
그럼 시작!
이 책은
혼혈 왕자의 소유다
잠 오는 콩을 자른다
칼날로 짓누르면
즙이 잘 나온다
How did you do that?
어떻게 한 거야?
You crush it. Don't cut it.
자르지 말고 칼날로 짓눌러
No. The instructions
specifically say to cut.
책엔 자르라고 나왔어
No, really.
아냐
콩 13개의 즙이 필요
Merlin's beard! It is perfect.
마법사 맙소사! 완벽해
So perfect I daresay
one drop would kill us all.
한 방울이면
우릴 다 죽이겠어
So here we are, then, as promised.
받아라, 약속한 대로
One vial of Felix Felicis.
펠릭스 펠리시스 한 병!
Congratulations.
축하한다
Use it well.
현명하게 쓰렴
Harry, you got my message. Come in.
내 전갈 받았구나
들어와라
How are you?
좀 어떠냐?
I'm fine, sir.
좋아요
Enjoying your classes?
수업은 재밌고?
I know Professor Slughorn
is most impressed with you.
슬러그혼 교수가
널 높이 사더구나
I think he overestimates my abilities, sir.
절 과대평가하신 거 같아요
Do you?
그래?
Definitely.
네
What about your activities
outside the classroom?
교실 밖 생활은 어떠냐?
- Sir?
- Well, I notice you spend...
- 네?
- 헤르미온느와
...a great deal of time with Miss Granger.
자주 어울리던데
I can't help wondering...
혹시…
Oh, no, no. I mean, she's brilliant,
and we're friends, but, no.
아뇨, 아녜요
저흰 그냥 친구예요
Forgive me. I was merely being curious.
미안하구나
호기심에 물어봤다
But enough chitchat.
잡담은 이쯤 하고
You must be wondering
why I summoned you here tonight.
왜 불렀는지 궁금하지?
The answer lies here.
대답은 이 안에 들었다
What you are looking at are memories.
기억이 들어 있지
In this case,
pertaining to one individual, Voldemort...
볼드모트와 관련된 기억
...or, as he was known then, Tom Riddle.
당시엔 톰 리들이었지만
This vial contains
the most particular memory...
이 병에 든 기억은
내가 그를
...of the day I first met him.
처음 만난 날이다
I'd like you to see it, if you would.
네가 봤으면 좋겠구나
I admit some confusion upon
receiving your letter, Mr. Dumbledore.
편지 받고
좀 혼란스러웠어요
고아원
In all the years Tom's been here,
he's never once had a family visitor.
톰을 면회 온 가족이
없었거든요
There have been incidents
with the other children. Nasty things.
다른 아이들한테
못된 짓을 많이 해요
Tom, you have a visitor.
톰, 손님 오셨다
How do you do, Tom?
반갑구나
Don't.
손대지 마요
- You're the doctor, aren't you?
- No.
- 의사죠?
- 아니
I am a professor.
난 교수야
I don't believe you.
못 믿어요
She wants me looked at.
원장님은 내가 미쳤대요
They think I'm different.
남들하고 다르다구요
Well, perhaps they're right.
어쩌면…
I'm not mad.
난 안 미쳤어요
Hogwarts is not a place for mad people.
호그와트는
정신병원이 아냐
Hogwarts is a school.
학교지
A school of magic.
마법을 가르치는…
You can do things, can't you, Tom?
네겐 특별한 능력이 있지?
Things other children can't.
다른 아이들은 못하는?
I can make things move
without touching them.
손 안 대고 물건을
옮길 수 있어요
I can make animals do what I want
without training them.
동물들을
내 맘대로 조종하고
I can make bad things happen
to people who are mean to me.
날 괴롭히는 사람들
혼내 주고
I can make them hurt...
고통 줄 수 있죠
...if I want.
내가 원하면…
Who are you?
누구세요?
Well, I'm like you, Tom.
나도 너처럼
I'm different.
딴 사람들과 달라
Prove it.
증명해 봐요
I think there's something in your wardrobe
trying to get out, Tom.
옷장에 뭔가를 숨겨 놨구나
Thievery is not tolerated at Hogwarts,
Tom.
호그와트에선
도둑질 용납 안 돼
At Hogwarts, you'll be taught not only
how to use magic, but how to control it.
마법을 쓰는 건 물론
통제하는 걸 배우지
You understand me?
알겠니?
I can speak to snakes too.
난 뱀과 말도 해요
They find me.
날 찾아와서
Whisper things.
말을 걸어요
Is that normal for someone like me?
나 같은 사람한텐
정상이에요?
Did you know, sir? Then?
아셨어요? 그때?
Did I know I'd just met the most
dangerous dark wizard of all time? No.
역사상 가장 사악한
마법사가 될 거란 걸? 아니
If I had, I...
알았다면…
Over time, while here at Hogwarts...
그는 호그와트에 있으면서
...Tom Riddle grew close
to one particular teacher.
한 교수와
아주 가깝게 지냈다
Can you guess
who that teacher might be?
누군지 알겠니?
You didn't bring Professor Slughorn back
simply to teach Potions, did you?
수업 때문에 슬러그혼 교수님
부른 게 아니군요
No, I did not.
그래, 아니다
You see, Professor Slughorn possesses
something I desire very dearly.
내가 원하는 걸 가졌는데
And he will not give it up easily.
쉽게 내놓지 않을 거야
You said Professor Slughorn
would try to collect me.
절 수제자로
삼을 거라 하셨죠?
I did.
그랬지
Do you want me to let him?
가깝게 지낼까요?
Yes.
그래
All right. Um...
좋아
This morning, I'm gonna be
putting you all through a few drills...
연습 경기를 통해
...just to assess your strengths.
너희들의 실력을 볼 거야
Quiet! Please!
조용히 좀 해
Shut it!
닥쳐!
Thanks. All right. Um...
고마워, 좋아
Just because you
made the team last year...
작년에 선수로 뛰었어도
...does not guarantee you a spot this year.
Is that clear?
탈락할 수 있어, 알았지?
Good.
좋아
No hard feelings, Weasley, all right?
기분 나쁘게 생각 마
Hard feelings?
뭘?
Yeah, I'll be going out for Keeper as well.
It's nothing personal.
나도 너처럼
파수꾼 자리 노리거든
Really? Strapping guy like you?
진짜? 너 같은 덩치는
You've got more of a Beater's build,
don't you think?
몰이꾼에 더 어울리잖아?
Keepers need to be quick, agile.
파수꾼은 재빠르고
민첩해야 돼
Oh, I like my chances.
나, 꽤 빨라
Say, think you could introduce me
to your friend Granger?
헤르미온느 좀 소개해 줄래?
Wouldn't mind getting on
a first-name basis, know what I mean?
친하게 지내고 싶거든
말뜻 알지?
Come on, Weasley!
잘해야 돼
- Come on, Ron!
- Go on, Weasley!
- 잘해, 론!
- 파이팅!
- Go on, Weasley!
- Yeah, Ron!
Go on, Cormac!
코맥, 파이팅!
Come on, Ron!
Come on, Ron.
잘해, 론
Confundus.
컨푼더스
Isn't he brilliant?
너무 멋있어!
I have to admit, I thought
I was gonna miss that last one.
마지막 공은
간신히 막아냈어
I hope Cormac's not taking it too hard.
코맥이 열 좀 받았겠어
He's got a bit of a thing for you,
Hermione. Cormac.
널 좋아하나 봐
He's vile.
난 걔 별로야
Have you ever heard of this spell?
Sectumsempra?
이 주문 들어 봤어?
섹튬셈프라?
No, I haven't.
아니
And if you had a shred of self-respect,
you'd hand that book in.
양심 있으면 그 책 반납해
Not bloody likely. He's top of the class.
무슨 소리!
덕분에 일등인데
He's even better than you, Hermione.
Slughorn thinks he's a genius.
널 제치고! 슬러그혼은
해리가 천재인 줄 알아
What?
왜?
I'd like to know whose that book was.
Let's have a look.
누구 책이었는지
알아야겠어, 보여 줘
No.
안돼
Why not?
왜?
The binding is fragile.
제본 상태가 별로야
- The binding is fragile?
- Yeah.
- 제본 상태가 별로라구?
- 응
- Who's the Half-Blood Prince?
- Who?
- 혼혈 왕자가 누구야?
- 누구?
That's what it says right here: "This book
is property of the Half-Blood Prince."
그렇게 적혔어
"혼혈 왕자의 소유다"
For weeks you carry around
this book, practically sleep with it...
몇 주 동안
잘 때도 끼고 자면서
... yet you have no desire to find out
who he is?
혼혈 왕자가 누군지
안 궁금해?
I didn't say I wasn't curious,
and I don't sleep with it.
아니라곤 안 했어
끼고 자지도 않고
Well, it's true.
아니긴!
I like a nice chat before I go to bed.
Now all you do is read that bloody book.
잠자리에서도
그 책만 읽잖아
It's just like being with Hermione.
헤르미온느처럼
책벌레 됐어
Well, I was curious, so I went to...
누군지 궁금해서…
- The library.
- The library. And?
- 도서관 갔군
- 알아냈어?
And nothing.
아니
I couldn't find a reference anywhere
to a Half-Blood Prince.
혼혈 왕자에 대해
아무 정보도 없어
- There we go. That settles it, then.
- Filius!
그럼 얘기 끝났네
I was hoping to find you
in the Three Broomsticks!
같이 한잔하겠소?
No, emergency choir practice,
I'm afraid, Horace.
아뇨, 갑자기
합창 연습이 생겨서
Does anyone fancy a Butterbeer?
버터 맥주 마실래?
A chum of mine
was sledging down Claxby Hill.
친구가
눈썰매 타러 갔었는데
We had a very long, homemade,
Norwegian-style sledge...
노르웨이 스타일
눈썰매가…
No, not there. Over here.
아니, 이쪽으로
No, sit beside me.
내 옆에 앉아
Okay.
알았어
Something to drink?
뭐 줄까?
Three Butterbeers,
and some ginger in mine, please.
버터 맥주 3잔요
Oh, bloody hell.
젠장
Slick git.
나쁜 자식
Honestly, Ronald,
they're only holding hands.
손만 잡았는데 뭘
And snogging.
키스도 하고!
- I'd like to leave.
- What?
- 난 갈래
- 뭐?
You can't be serious.
농담이지?
- That happens to be my sister.
- So?
- 내 동생이거든?
- 그래서?
What if she looked over here and saw you
snogging me? You expect her to leave?
우리가 키스하는 걸 보면
네 동생도 가 버릴까?
- Hey, my boy!
- Hello, sir. Wonderful to see you.
- 해리!
- 안녕하세요, 교수님
And you, and you.
그래, 그래
So, what brings you here?
여긴 어떻게?
The Three Broomsticks and I go way back,
further than I care to admit.
난 옛날부터
이 술집 단골이었어
I can remember
when it was One Broomstick.
술집과 내가
같이 늙어 가는 거지
All hands on deck, Granger.
Listen, my boy, in the old days...
나의 실수! 옛날처럼
...I used to throw together
the occasional supper party...
학생들을 초대해
저녁을 먹을 거야
...for the select student or two.
우수한 학생들만…
- Would you be game?
- I'd consider it an honor, sir.
- 관심 있냐?
- 저야 영광이죠
You would be welcome too, Granger.
너도 오렴, 헤르미온느
- I'd be delighted, sir.
- Splendid. Look for my owl.
- 감사합니다
- 좋아, 부엉이 통해 연락하마
Good to see you, Wallenby.
반가웠다, 왈렌비
What are you playing at?
무슨 꿍꿍이야?
Dumbledore's asked me
to get to know him.
덤블도어가 친해지래
- Get to know him?
- I don't know.
- 왜?
- 나도 몰라
It must be important.
If it wasn't, Dumbledore wouldn't ask.
중요한 일이 분명해
아님 안 시키셨겠지
Got a little bit...
입가에…
Katie, you don't know what it could be.
케이티, 만지지 마
- Harry.
- What?
걱정 마
Did you hear what she said back
at the pub about me and her snogging?
내가 미쳤냐?
자기랑 키스를 하게?
As if.
웃겨
I warned her.
I warned her not to touch it.
난 말렸어
만지지 말랬다구
Don't get any closer.
Get back, all of you.
가까이 가지 마, 물러서!
괜찮아
괜찮아, 괜찮아
Do not touch that, except by
the wrappings. Do you understand?
포장지 외엔 손대지 마
알았어?
You're sure Katie did not have this
in her possession...
케이티가 그 술집에 갈 때
...when she entered
the Three Broomsticks?
안 가져간 게 확실해?
It's like I said.
틀림없어요
She left to go to the loo, and when
she came back she had the package.
화장실 갔다가
그걸 갖고 와선
She said it was important
that she deliver it.
전해 줘야 한댔어요
- Did she say to whom?
- To Professor Dumbledore.
- 누구한테?
- 덤블도어 교수님요
Very well. Thank you, Leanne.
You may go.
고맙다, 그만 가 봐라
Why is it when something happens
it is always you three?
왜 너희 셋이 가는 곳마다
말썽이 생기지?
Believe me, professor, I've been asking
myself the same question for six years.
내 말요, 저도 6년 동안
그게 궁금했어요
McGONAGALL:
Oh, Severus.
스네이프
What do you think?
어때요?
I think Miss Bell is lucky to be alive.
케이티가
살아 있는 게 기적이군요
She was cursed, wasn't she?
저주에 걸린 거죠?
I know Katie. Off the pitch,
she wouldn't hurt a fly.
걘 파리도 못 죽일 아이예요
If she was delivering that to Dumbledore,
she wasn't doing it knowingly.
저주에 걸린 걸 모르고
전하려 했을 거예요
Yes, she was cursed.
그래, 저주에 걸렸다
It was Malfoy.
말포이 짓이에요
That is a very serious accusation, Potter.
아무나
함부로 의심하면 안 돼
Indeed.
그래
- Your evidence?
- I just know.
- 증거는?
- 그냥 알아요
You just...
그냥…
...know.
안다구?
You astonish with your gifts, Potter.
정말 대단하구나
Gifts mere mortals
can only dream of possessing.
점쟁이의 능력까지
갖게 됐으니
How grand it must be
to be the Chosen One.
선택받은 자인 게
아주 뿌듯하겠어
I suggest you go back to your dormitories.
All of you.
기숙사로 돌아가, 전부 다!
What do you suppose
Dean sees in her? Ginny?
딘은 지니의
어디가 좋은 걸까?
Well, what does she see in him?
그럼 지니는?
Dean? He's brilliant.
딘? 똑똑하잖아
You called him a slick git
not five hours ago.
아깐 나쁜 놈이라며?
Yeah, well, he was running his hands
all over my sister, wasn't he?
내 여동생 몸을 더듬었잖아
Something snaps, and you've gotta
hate him, you know? On principle.
세상에 어떤 오빠가
기분 안 나쁘겠냐?
I suppose.
하긴
- So, what is it he sees in her?
- I don't know.
- 지니가 왜 좋을까?
- 글쎄
She's smart, funny.
똑똑하고 재밌잖아
- Attractive.
- Attractive?
- 매력 넘치고
- 매력?
- You know, she's got nice skin.
- Skin?
- 피부도 좋잖아
- 피부?
Dean dates my sister
because of her skin?
피부가 좋아서 좋아한다구?
Well, no, I mean, I'm just saying
it could be a contributing factor.
그건 아니지만
피부 좋아서 나쁠 건 없지
Hermione's got nice skin.
헤르미온느도 피부 좋은데
Wouldn't you say? As skin goes, I mean.
완전 매끈매끈
피부 미인이야
I've never really thought about it.
생각 안 해봤는데
But, I suppose, yeah.
그런 거 같네
Very nice.
아주 좋지
- I think I'll be going to sleep now.
- Right. Yeah.
- 난 잘래
- 그래
So tell me, Cormac, do you see anything
of your Uncle Tiberius these days?
코맥, 삼촌은 잘 계시냐?
Yes, sir. In fact,
I'm meant to go hunting with him...
네
삼촌, 마법부 장관님과
...and the Minister for Magic
over the holidays.
사냥 가기로 했죠
Well, be sure to give them both my best.
만나면 안부 전해 주렴
What about your uncle, Belby?
너희 삼촌은, 벨비?
For those who don't know, Marcus'
uncle invented the Wolfsbane Potion.
울프스베인 마법약을
만든 분이시지
- Is he working on anything new?
- Don't know.
- 요즘은 뭘 만들지?
- 몰라요
Him and Dad don't get on. Probably
because me dad says potions are rubbish.
아버진 마법약은
전부 쓰레기래요
Says the only potion worth having
is a stiff one at the end of the day.
술이 최고의
마법약이라 하시죠
What about you, Miss Granger? What does
your family do in the Muggle world?
헤르미온느
부모님이 머글인데 하시는 일이?
My parents are dentists.
치과 의사세요
They tend to people's teeth.
이빨을 치료하죠
Fascinating. And is that considered
a dangerous profession?
흥미롭구나
위험한 직업이니?
No.
아뇨
Although, one boy, Robbie Fenwick,
did bite my father once.
아빠가 꼬마한테
물린 적은 있지만요
He needed 10 stitches.
10바늘 꿰맸죠
Ah. Miss Weasley. Come in, come in.
지니 왔구나, 들어오렴
Look at her eyes.
They've been fighting again, her and Dean.
눈을 봐
딘이랑 또 싸웠나 봐
Sorry. I'm not usually late.
늦어서 죄송해요
No matter. You're just in time for dessert,
that is, if Belby's left you any.
괜찮다, 디저트는 먹겠구나
벨비가 남겨 놨으면!
What?
왜?
Nothing.
아냐
Goodbye. Bye-bye.
잘 가렴
- Potter.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- 포터
- 죄송해요
I was just admiring your hourglass.
모래시계 구경하느라
Oh, yes.
그래
A most intriguing object.
매혹적인 물건이지
The sand runs in accordance
with the quality of the conversation.
대화 수준에 맞춰
모래가 떨어지는데
If it is stimulating, the sand runs slowly.
수준이 높으면
천천히 떨어지고
- If it is not...
- I think I'll be going.
- 반대면…
- 전 그만 갈게요
Nonsense.
You have nothing to fear, dear boy.
무슨 소리!
무서워할 거 없어
As to some of your classmates...
다른 학생들은
...well, let's just say they're unlikely
to make the shelf.
내 선반에 올라갈
가능성이 없어
The shelf, sir?
선반이라뇨?
Anyone who aspires to be anyone
hopes to end up here.
큰 인물이 될
학생들만 올라가지
But then again, you already are someone,
aren't you, Harry?
하지만 넌 벌써
유명하잖아, 해리
Did Voldemort ever make the shelf, sir?
볼드모트도 올라갔나요?
You knew him, didn't you, sir,
Tom Riddle? You were his teacher.
톰 리들 아시죠?
제자였잖아요
Mr. Riddle had a number of teachers
whilst here at Hogwarts.
리들을 가르친 교수는 많았어
What was he like?
어떤 사람이었죠?
I'm sorry, sir. Forgive me.
죄송하지만 알고 싶어요
He killed my parents.
제 부모님을 죽인 자니까…
Of course.
그래
It's only natural
you should want to know more.
궁금한 것도 당연하지
But I'm afraid I must disappoint you,
Harry.
하지만 실망시켜
미안하구나
When I first met Mr. Riddle,
he was a quiet...
처음 리들을 만났을 땐
...albeit brilliant, boy committed
to becoming a first-rate wizard.
위대한 마법사가 될
인재였다
Not unlike others I've known.
다른 학생들과 달랐지
Not unlike yourself, in fact.
너하고도 달랐어
If the monster existed...
마음 깊은 곳에
...it was buried deep within.
괴물이 존재했던 거야
Good luck, eh, Ron.
굿럭, 론
- Nice hat!
- Ron, you're a loser.
- 모자 멋진데!
- 바보 자식
I'm counting on you, Ron.
I have two Galleons on Gryffindor, yeah?
너만 믿는다
2갈레온 걸었어
- Looking good, Ron.
- Loser!
찌질이!
What's he wearing?
옷 꼬라지 봐!
So how was it, then?
어땠어?
- How was what?
- Your dinner party?
- 뭐가?
- 슬러그혼 파티
Pretty boring, actually.
너무 지루했어
Though I think Harry enjoyed dessert.
해리는 누가 와서
좋았겠지만!
Slughorn's having a Christmas do,
you know.
성탄절 파티에
And we're meant to bring someone.
파트너 데려가야 돼
I expect you'll be bringing McLaggen.
He's in the Slug Club, isn't he?
코맥이랑 갈 거지?
- Actually, I was going to ask you.
- Really?
- 너랑 가려고 했어
- 진짜?
Good luck today, Ron.
행운을 빌어, 론
I know you'll be brilliant.
틀림없이 잘할 거야
I'm resigning. After today's match,
McLaggen can have my spot.
시합 끝나고 코맥한테
내 포지션 넘길래
Have it your way.
좋을 대로 해
- Juice?
- Sure.
- 주스?
- 응
Hello, everyone.
안녕, 얘들아
You look dreadful, Ron.
안색이 안 좋아, 론
Is that why you put something
in his cup?
그래서 주스에 약 탄 거니?
Is it a tonic?
영양제야?
Liquid luck.
행운의 물약
Don't drink it, Ron.
마시지 마!
- You could be expelled for that.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- 퇴학당할 수 있어
- 무슨 소린지 모르겠네
Come on, Harry.
We've got a game to win.
시합 이기러 가자구
Yes!
예스!
Go on, Ron! Do it!
Weasley! Weasley! Weasley!
Yes!
위즐리!
Whoo!
Yes. Whoo!
Weasley! Weasley! Weasley!
위즐리!
You really shouldn't have done it.
약 탄 건 잘못이야
I know. I suppose I could've
just used a Confundus Charm.
알아, 그냥 컨푼더스
마법을 쓸 걸 그랬나?
That was different. That was tryouts.
This was an actual game.
그때랑은 달라
이건 진짜 시합이었어
You didn't put it in.
안 탔구나
Ron only thought you did.
론은 탄 줄 알고?
Charms spell. I'm just practicing.
주문 연습 중이야
Well, they're really good.
새들이 진짜 같아
How does it feel, Harry?
어떤 기분이야?
When you see Dean with Ginny?
딘과 지니가
같이 있는 걸 보면?
I know.
난 알아
I see the way you look at her.
걔를 바라보는
네 표정 봤거든
You're my best friend.
우린 친구잖아
Oops.
웁스!
I think this room's taken.
딴 데로 가자
What's with the birds?
새들은 뭐야?
Oppugno.
옵푸그노!
It feels like this.
지금 네 기분과 똑같아
Look, I can't help it
if she's got her knickers in a twist.
내가 왜 헤르미온느를
신경 써야 하는데?
What Lav and I have, well,
let's just say, there's no stopping it.
라벤더와 난 아주 뜨겁다구
It's chemical.
불꽃처럼!
Will it last? Who knows?
Point is, I'm a free agent.
영원할 거라곤 장담 못 하지만
누굴 만나든 내 맘이잖아
He's at perfect liberty
to kiss whoever he likes.
걔가 누구랑 키스하든
난 관심 없어
I really couldn't care less.
Was I under the impression he and I would
be attending Slughorn's Christmas party?
슬러그혼 파티에
데려갈 생각 했냐구?
Yes.
그래
Now, given the circumstances,
I've had to make other arrangements.
그치만 상관없어
대타 구했으니까
Have you?
그래?
Yes. Why?
응, 왜?
I just thought, seeing as neither of us
can go with who we'd really like to...
우리 둘 다
좋아하는 사람하고 못 가니까
...we should go together, as friends.
같이 가면 되잖아
친구로서…
Why didn't I think of that?
왜 그 생각을 못 했지?
Who are you going with?
누구랑 갈 건데?
Um, it's a surprise.
비밀이야
Anyway, it's you we've got to worry
about. You can't just take anyone.
네 걱정이나 해
아무나 데려가면 안 돼
See that girl over there?
쟤 보이지?
That's Romilda Vane. Apparently she's
trying to smuggle you a love potion.
로밀다야
네게 사랑의 묘약을 보내려고 한대
Really?
진짜?
Hey! She's only interested in you because
she thinks you're the Chosen One.
네가 선택받은 자라고 생각해
관심 있는 거야
But I am the Chosen One.
선택받은 자 맞는걸
Okay, sorry. Um, kidding.
미안, 농담이야
I'll ask someone I like.
데려갈 사람 있어
Someone cool.
멋진 아이
I've never been to this part of the castle.
이쪽엔 처음 와 봐
At least not while awake.
I sleepwalk, you see.
깨있을 땐!
나 몽유병 있거든
That's why I wear shoes to bed.
그래서 잘 때도
신발을 안 벗어
Harmonia Nectere Passus.
하모니아 넥테르
파서스
Harmonia Nectere Passus.
하모니아 넥테르
파서스
Harmonia Nectere Passus.
하모니아 넥테르
파서스
Drink?
마실래?
Neville.
네빌
I didn't get into the Slug Club.
초대 못 받아서…
It's okay, though. He's got Belby
handing out towels in the loo.
벨비보단 낫지
걘 화장실 담당인걸
- Oh, well, I'm fine, mate. Thanks.
- Okay.
- 마실 건 됐어
- 그래
Hermione. What are you doing?
And what happened to you?
여기서 뭐 해?
무슨 일이야?
I've just escaped.
I mean, left Cormac under the mistletoe.
도망쳤어
코맥이랑 키스하기 싫어서
Cormac? That's who you invited?
코맥? 걔를 데려온 거야?
I thought it would annoy Ron the most.
론이 질투하게 만들려고
Thank you. I'll catch up with you later.
고맙네, 그럼 나중에
He's got more tentacles
than a Snarfalump plant.
코맥은 완전히 바람둥이야
- Dragon tartare?
- No, I'm fine. Thank you.
- 용의 타르타르?
- 아니
Just as well.
They give one horribly bad breath.
잘 생각했어
먹으면 입 냄새 장난 아냐
On second thoughts...
마음 바꿨어
Might keep Cormac at bay.
코맥이 키스 않게!
Oh, God, here he comes.
맙소사, 저기 온다
I think she just went to powder her nose.
화장 고치러 갔어
Slippery little minx, your friend.
자꾸 날 피해
Likes to work her mouth too,
doesn't she?
수다 장난 아니지?
재잘재잘
What is this I'm eating, by the way?
뭘로 만든 거야?
Dragon balls.
용 거시기
You've just bought yourself
a month's detention, McLaggen.
한 달간 근신 처분이다
코맥
Not so quick, Potter.
어딜, 포터
Sir, I really think I should
rejoin the party. My date...
파트너가 기다려서…
Can surely survive your absence
for another minute or two.
잠깐 늦는다고
문제 될 거 없겠지
Besides, I only wish
to convey a message.
네게 전할 메시지가 있다
- A message?
- From Professor Dumbledore.
- 메시지요?
- 덤블도어 교수님이
He asked me to give you his best,
and he hopes you enjoy your holiday.
크리스마스 연휴
잘 보내라더구나
You see...
여행 가셨는데
...he's traveling, and he won't
return until term resumes.
개학 전엔 안 돌아오신다
Traveling where?
어디로요?
Take your hands off me, you filthy Squib!
더러운 손 치워!
Professor Slughorn, sir.
슬러그혼 교수님
I just discovered this boy
lurking in an upstairs corridor.
위층 복도에
숨어 있는 걸 찾았죠
He claims to have been
invited to your party.
파티에 초대받았다더군요
Okay, okay. I was gatecrashing. Happy?
초대 안 받고 왔어요
됐어요?
내가 데려가겠소
I'll escort him out.
Certainly, professor.
그러시죠, 교수님
All right, everyone, carry on, carry on.
모두 계속 즐겨, 즐기라구
Maybe I did hex that Bell girl.
Maybe I didn't. What's it to you?
그 여자애한테 저주 걸든 말든
무슨 상관이에요?
I swore to protect you.
널 보호하겠다고
I made the Unbreakable Vow.
깨뜨릴 수 없는 맹세를 했다
I don't need protection.
보호는 필요 없어요
I was chosen for this.
Out of all others. Me.
난 선택받았어요
그분께 직접!
- 실패 안 해요
- 겁에 질렸잖아
- And I won't fail him.
- You're afraid, Draco.
You attempt to conceal it,
but it's obvious. Let me assist you.
얼굴에 쓰여 있어
내가 도와주마
No!
싫어요!
난 선택받았어요!
내가 할 일이에요!
I was chosen. This is my moment.
"깨뜨릴 수 없는 맹세"?
"Unbreakable Vow."
You're sure that's what Snape said?
제대로 들은 거야?
확실해, 왜?
Positive. Why?
Well, it's just you can't break
an Unbreakable Vow.
깨뜨릴 수 없는 맹세는
어길 수 없어
I'd worked that much out for myself,
funnily enough.
그쯤은 나도 알아
You don't understand.
넌 몰라
Oh, bloody hell.
젠장
I miss you.
보고 싶을 거야
Lovely.
귀엽네
All she wants to do is snog me.
My lips are getting chapped. Look.
키스에 미친 애야
입술 다 텄어, 봐
됐어, 믿을게
I'll take your word for it.
So, what happens to you? What happens
if you break an Unbreakable Vow?
어떻게 돼?
깨뜨릴 수 없는 맹세를 어기면?
You die.
죽어
Wait, the pudding's still here.
Voldemort has chosen
Draco Malfoy for a mission?
볼드모트가
드레이코를 선택했다?
I know it sounds mad.
저도 안 믿어져요
Has it occurred to you Snape was
simply pretending to offer Draco help...
스네이프가
녀석 속셈 캐내려고
...so he could find out
what he was up to?
도와주는 척하는 건
아닐까?
- That's not what it sounded like.
- Perhaps Harry's right.
- 아닌 거 같았어요
- 해리가 옳아
To make an Unbreakable Vow, it's...
깨뜨릴 수 없는…
It comes down to whether or not
you trust Dumbledore's judgment.
덤블도어의
판단력을 믿어야 돼
- Dumbledore trusts Snape, therefore I do.
- Dumbledore can make mistakes.
- 그는 스네이프를 신뢰한다구
- 실수라면요?
You're blinded by hatred.
- 증오심에 눈이 멀었군
- 아녜요!
- I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
기사단 사람들이
사라져가고 있어
People are disappearing, Harry, daily.
We place our trust
in a handful of people.
아무나 못 믿을 상황인데
If we start fighting amongst ourselves,
we're doomed.
내분이 일어나면
모든 게 끝장이야
Open up, you.
입 벌려
Don't you trust me?
날 못 믿어?
It's good.
맛있네
Yeah, I'll just... Get... Yeah.
자리 좀…
- Pie?
- Not for me, no.
- 파이 먹을래?
- 아니
You'll have to forgive Remus.
리무스를 이해하렴
It takes its toll, his condition.
늑대인간들이
좀 예민하잖아
Are you all right, Mr. Weasley?
괜찮으세요, 위즐리 아저씨?
We're being followed, all of us.
항상 미행이 붙어
Most days,
Molly doesn't leave the house.
몰리는 집 안에만 있고
It's not been easy.
쉽질 않아
Did you get my owl?
제 메시지 받으셨어요?
Yes, I did.
그래
If Dumbledore's traveling,
then that's news to the Ministry...
덤블도어가 여행 간 걸
마법부에선 몰라
...but perhaps that's the way
Dumbledore wants it.
비밀로 하고 싶으셨겠지
As for Draco Malfoy...
드레이코 일은
...I know a bit more.
좀 알아봤다
- Go on.
- I sent an agent to Borgin and Burkes.
- 말씀하세요
- 그 가게에 사람을 보냈었는데
I think, from what you described...
네가 설명한 걸 미루어 볼 때
...what you and Ron saw in summer...
너와 론이 본
...the object
that Draco is so interested in...
드레이코가
관심 가진 물건은
...is a vanishing cabinet.
사라지는 캐비닛이야
A vanishing cabinet?
사라지는 캐비닛?
They were all the rage
when Voldemort first rose to power.
볼드모트가 등장했을 때
유행했었다
You can see the appeal.
Should Death Eaters come knocking...
이유 알겠지?
죽음을 먹는 자를 피해
...one simply had to slip inside
and disappear for an hour or two.
그 안에 들어가서
잠깐 사라지는 거지
They can transport you anywhere.
순간 이동하는 건데
Tricky contraptions though,
very temperamental.
아주 위험한 물건이다
예측불허고
What happened to it?
The one at Borgin and Burkes?
그 가게 캐비닛은
어떻게 됐죠?
Nothing.
그대로야
It's still there.
아직 가게에 있어
It was delicious, Molly, really.
- 맛있었어요, 몰리
- 진짜 갈래요?
Are you sure you won't stay?
가야 돼요
곧 달이 바뀌어서…
No, we should go. The first night
of the cycle's always the worst.
Remus?
리무스?
Sweetheart.
자기야?
Has Ron gone to bed?
론은 자?
Um... Not yet. No.
아니, 아직
Shoelace.
신발끈이…
Merry Christmas, Harry.
메리 크리스마스, 해리
메리 크리스마스
Merry Christmas.
- Harry, no!
- Remus!
- 해리, 안돼!
- 리무스!
Ginny!
지니!
I killed Sirius Black!
내가 시리우스 블랙을
죽였다!
You coming to get me?
날 잡아 봐!
Harry, can you get me?
You coming to get me?
날 잡을 수 있어, 해리?
Harry?
해리?
Stupefy!
스투페파이!
Harry!
해리!
지니…
Ginny!
지니!
Molly.
몰리
It's easy for them to get to you.
넌 쉽게 추적당해
You're bloody lucky you weren't killed.
You have to realize who you are, Harry.
안 죽은 게 행운이야
앞으론 더 조심해
I know who I am, Hermione, all right?
잔소리 좀 그만해!
미안해
Sorry.
Lav, come on. Of course I'll wear it.
알았어, 항상 차고 다닐게
That's my Won-Won.
내 로온 로온
Excuse me, I have to go and vomit.
미안, 난 토하고 올게
I'd like to know
where you get your information.
어떻게 알아냈지?
More knowledgeable
than half the staff, you are.
교수들보다 더 똑똑하구나
Sir...
교수님…
...is it true
that Professor Merrythought is retiring?
메리쏘우트 교수님이
은퇴한다면서요?
Now, Tom.
I couldn't tell you if I knew, could I?
알아도 말 못해 줘
By the way, thank you for the pineapple.
You're quite right, it is my favorite.
파인애플 고맙다
제일 좋아하는데
But how did you know?
어떻게 알았지?
Intuition.
직관이죠
벌써 시간이?
Gracious. Is it that time already?
Off you go, boys, or Professor Dippet
will have us all in detention.
그만 가렴
잘못하면 근신 당할라
Look sharp, Tom. Don't want to be caught
out of bed after hours.
빨리 가, 톰
취침 시간 지났어
- Is something on your mind, Tom?
- Yes, sir.
- 내게 할 말 있냐?
- 네
You see, I couldn't think
of anyone else to go to.
물어볼 사람이
교수님뿐이에요
The other professors,
well, they're not like you.
다른 분들은
교수님 같질 않아요
They might misunderstand.
오해할 거예요
Go on.
말해 봐
I was in the library the other night...
도서관에 갔다가
...in the Restricted Section...
금서 구역에서
...and I read something rather odd
about a bit of rare magic.
이상한 마법에 관한
책을 읽었는데
And I thought perhaps
you could illuminate me.
교수님이
뭔지 좀 가르쳐 주세요
It's called, as I understand it...
그 마법의 이름은…
I beg your pardon?
뭐라구?
I don't know anything about such things,
and if I did, I wouldn't tell you!
난 그런 거 몰라
알아도 못 가르쳐 줘!
Now, get out of here at once, and don't
let me ever catch you mentioning it again!
당장 나가라
다신 그 얘기 하지 마!
Confused?
혼란스럽지?
I'd be surprised if you weren't.
아니라면 이상하지
Well, I don't understand.
What happened?
이해가 안 돼요
어떻게 된 거죠?
This is perhaps the most important
memory I've collected.
내가 찾아낸 기억 중
가장 중요한데
It is also a lie.
다 거짓이야
This memory has been tampered with...
조작됐지
...by the same person whose memory it is,
our old friend, Professor Slughorn.
기억의 주인인
슬러그혼에 의해
But why would he tamper
with his own memory?
왜 자기 기억을 조작해요?
- I suspect he's ashamed of it.
- Why?
- 수치스러웠겠지
- 왜요?
Why, indeed?
바로 그거야
I asked you to get to know
Professor Slughorn, and you have done so.
슬러그혼과 친해졌으니까
Now I want you to persuade him
to divulge his true memory...
그를 잘 설득해서
진짜 기억을
...any way you can.
알아내
I don't know him that well, sir.
그럴 정도로 안 친해요
This memory is everything.
그 기억을 모르면
Without it, we are blind.
우린 장님이나 다름없다
Without it, we leave the fate
of our world to chance.
세상의 운명을
운에 맡겨야 하지
You have no choice.
네겐 선택의 여지가 없다
You must not fail.
실패해선 안 돼
So I'd highly recommend
you reacquaint yourself...
해독제에 대해
반드시 복습하도록
...with the chapter on antidotes.
I'll tell you more about bezoars
in our next class. Right, off you go.
위석에 대해선
다음 시간에, 이상
Alys, don't forget your rat tail.
알리스! 쥐꼬리 챙겨야지
Aha. If it isn't
the Prince of Potions himself.
마법약 왕자님이 오셨구만
To what do I owe this pleasure?
무슨 일로?
Sir, I wondered
if I might ask you something.
여쭤 볼 게 있어서요
Ask away, dear boy, ask away.
뭐든지 물어봐
The other day I was in the library,
in the Restricted Section...
도서관에 갔다가
금서 구역에서
...and I came across something rather odd
about a very rare piece of magic.
이상한 마법에 관한
책을 읽었어요
Yes. And what was this
rare piece of magic?
그 이상한 마법이 뭐지?
Well, I don't know.
I can't remember the name exactly.
모르겠어요
이름이 기억 안 나요
It got me wondering, are there some kinds
of magic you're not allowed to teach us?
우리한테 못 가르치는
마법도 있나요?
I'm Potions Master, Harry.
그런 건 스네이프 교수한테
물어봐야지
I think your question'd
better be posed to Professor Snape.
Yes. Um...
네
He and I don't exactly
see eye to eye, sir.
근데 그 교수님과
친하질 않아서
What I mean to say is...
제 말은
...well, he's not like you.
교수님 같질 않아요
He might misunderstand.
오해할 거예요
Yes. There can be no light
without the dark.
어둠이 없다면
빛도 없는 법이지
And so it is with magic. Myself, I always
strive to live within the light.
마법도 마찬가지야
난 빛을 믿는다
I suggest you do the same.
너도 그러렴
Is that what you told Tom Riddle,
when he came asking questions?
톰 리들한테도
그렇게 말하셨어요?
Dumbledore put you up to this,
didn't he?
덤블도어가 시킨 거지?
Didn't he?
그렇지?
네?
Yes?
Oh, it's you, Potter.
해리구나
I'm sorry, I'm busy at the moment.
미안하다, 지금 좀 바빠서
It's beautiful, isn't it? The moon.
참 아름답지? 달 말이야
Divine.
그래
Had ourselves a little
late-night snack, did we?
초콜릿 먹었어?
It was on your bed, the box.
I just thought I'd try one.
네 침대에 있길래
하나 먹었어
- Or 20.
- I can't stop thinking about her, Harry.
- 20개겠지!
- 자꾸 그녀가 생각나
Honestly, I reckoned
she was annoying you.
귀찮다고 할 땐 언제고?
She could never annoy me.
귀찮다니!
I think I love her.
나, 사랑에 빠졌어
Well, brilliant.
잘됐네
Do you think she knows I exist?
그녀가 내 존재를 알까?
I hope so. She's been snogging you
for three months.
당연하지
석 달 동안 키스했잖아
Snogging? Who are you talking about?
키스? 누굴 말하는 거야?
Who are you talking about?
넌?
Romilda, of course. Romilda Vane.
그야 로밀다지, 로밀다 베인
Okay, very funny.
농담하지 마
- What was that for?
- It's no joke! I'm in love with her!
- 뭐야?
- 농담 아냐! 그녀를 사랑해!
Fine, you're in love with her.
Have you ever actually met her?
그래, 사랑한다고 쳐
만나 보긴 했어?
No. Can you introduce me?
아니, 소개해 줄래?
Come on, Ron. I'm gonna introduce you
to Romilda Vane.
가자, 로밀다 소개해 줄게
해리
항상 널 생각해
로밀다
I'm sorry, sir. I wouldn't bother you
if it weren't absolutely essential.
죄송하지만
중요한 일이라서요
Where's Romilda?
로밀다 어디 있어?
What's the matter with Wenby?
얘 왜 이래?
Very powerful love potion.
사랑의 묘약에 취했어요
Very well. Better bring him in.
좋아, 들어와
I'd have thought you could whip up
a remedy for this in no time, Harry.
이런 해독제쯤은
만들 줄 알잖아
Well, I thought this called
for a more practiced hand, sir.
최고가 만드는 게
좋을 거 같아서요
Hello, darling. Fancy a drink?
안녕, 자기야, 한잔할래?
Perhaps you're right.
완전히 맛 갔군
I'm sorry, by the way, professor,
about earlier today, our misunderstanding.
아까 일은 죄송해요
제가 오해했어요
Oh, not at all. All water
under the bridge, you know? Correct?
괜찮다, 잊어버려
지난 일이잖아
I expect you're tired of it
after all these years.
진절머리나겠어요
All the questions about Voldemort.
볼드모트에 대한 질문들…
Don't use that name.
그 이름 말하지 마!
There you are, old boy. Bottoms up.
여기, 쭉 마셔
- What's this?
- Tonic for the nerves.
- 뭐죠?
- 몸에 좋은 거야
- What happened to me?
- Love potion.
- 내가 왜?
- 사랑의 묘약!
A bloody strong one at that.
아주 강력한 거였지
- I feel really bad.
- You need a pick-me-up.
- 기분이 꽝이야
- 술이면 해결돼
Got Butterbeer,
wine, dazzling oak-matured mead.
버터 맥주, 와인
숙성시킨 벌꿀 술
I had other intentions for this,
but I think, given the circumstances...
선물할 술이지만
상황이 상황인 만큼…
Here we are, Potter.
받아라
To life!
인생을 위하여!
Ron.
론!
Ron. Professor, do something.
어떻게 좀 해봐요!
I don't understand.
이해가 안 돼
Come on, Ron, breathe.
론, 숨 쉬어
These girls, they're gonna kill me.
난 여자 때문에
일찍 죽을 거야
Quick thinking on your part, Harry,
using a bezoar.
위석을 쓴 건
훌륭했다, 해리
You must be very proud
of your student, Horace.
제자가 대견하겠군
Hm? Oh, yes, very proud.
대견하고말고
I think we agree,
Potter's actions were heroic.
포터 행동은
칭찬할 만하지만
The question is,
why were they necessary?
왜 그런 상황이 생긴 거죠?
Why, indeed?
그래, 왜지?
This appears to be a gift, Horace.
선물 받은 거 같은데
You don't remember
who gave you this bottle?
누가 준 건지 기억하나?
Which, by the way, possesses remarkably
subtle hints of licorice and cherry...
감초와 체리 향이
옅게 나지만
...when not polluted with poison.
독이 들어 있어
Actually I had intended
to give it as a gift myself.
실은, 내가 선물로
주려던 걸세
To whom, I might ask?
누구한테?
To you, Headmaster.
자네한테!
Where is he?
어디 있어?
Where's my Won-Won?
Has he been asking for me?
내 로온 로온 어디 있어?
날 찾아?
What's she doing here?
쟤가 왜 여기 있어?
I might ask you the same question.
누가 할 소린데?
I happen to be his girlfriend.
난 론의 여자 친구거든
I happen to be his friend.
난 론의… 친구야
Don't make me laugh.
You haven't spoken in weeks.
웃기고 있네
서로 말도 않으면서
I suppose you want to make up
now that he's all interesting.
이번 사고로 뜨니까
갑자기 좋아지니?
He's been poisoned, you daft dimbo!
독약 때문에 죽을 뻔했어!
And for the record,
I've always found him interesting.
또 별 볼 일 없을 때도
좋아했구
Ah. See? He senses my presence.
봤지? 내가 온 걸 안 거야
Don't worry, Won-Won. I'm here.
걱정 마, 내 로온 로온
내가 왔어
I'm here.
Uh... Hermione...
Hermione.
헤르미…
헤르미온느
Oh, to be young,
and to feel love's keen sting.
사랑은 원래 아픈 거지
Well, come away, everybody.
그만 가자
Mr. Weasley is well tended.
위즐리는 걱정 마
About time, don't you think?
이제야 둘이 연결됐네
Thank you.
고마워요
Oh, shut up.
아무 말 마
보진과 버크
1863년 개업
Stop it, Ron. You're making it snow.
그만해, 론
눈이 내리잖아
Tell me how I broke up
with Lavender again.
내가 라벤더랑
어떻게 깨졌다구?
Um, well...
...she came to visit you
in the hospital.
그게… 걔가 문병 왔는데
And you talked.
네가 말했어
I don't believe it was
a particularly long conversation.
그냥 짧은 한 단어로…
Don't get me wrong, I'm bloody thrilled
to be shot of her.
오해하진 마
깨져서 좋긴 한데
It's just she seems a bit put out.
너무 살벌하게 노려봐서
Yes, she does, doesn't she?
그러게, 표정 장난 아니다
You say you don't remember
anything from that night?
뭐라고 했는지 기억 안 나?
Anything at all?
전혀?
There is something.
확실친 않은데…
But it can't be.
I was completely boggled, wasn't I?
말도 안 돼
나, 제정신 아니었잖아
Right. Boggled.
그래, 제정신 아니었지
섹튬셈프라 - 적에게 사용
Harry.
해리
That's Katie.
케이티야
Katie Bell.
케이티 벨
Katie. How are you?
케이티, 좀 어때?
I know you're going to ask, Harry,
but I don't know who cursed me.
물어볼 줄 알았어
그치만 누가 저주 건진 몰라
I've been trying to remember, honestly.
기억해 내려고
아무리 애써 봐도
But I just can't.
소용이 없어
Katie?
케이티?
I know what you did, Malfoy.
You hexed her, didn't you?
난 알아, 말포이
네가 저주를 건 거지?
Sectumsempra!
섹튬셈프라!
Vulnera Sanentur.
불네라 사넨투르
You have to get rid of it. Today.
그 책을 없애, 오늘 당장!
Take my hand.
내 손 잡아
The Room of Requirement.
필요의 방…
We need to hide
the Half-Blood Prince's book...
혼혈 왕자의 책을
여기 숨기는 거야
...where no one will ever find it,
including you.
널 포함해 아무도 못 찾게
- What was that?
- 뭐지?
See?
봤지?
You never know what you'll find up here.
여긴 별의별 게 다 있어
All right, close your eyes.
That way you can't be tempted.
눈 감아
어디 숨긴지 모르게
Close your eyes.
눈을 감아
That can stay hidden up here too,
if you like.
우리 키스도 여기 숨겨 놓자
So did you and Ginny do it, then?
지니랑 했어?
What?
뭐?
You know, hide the book?
책 숨겼냐구
Oh, yeah.
응
Ah. Dear, yes.
그래
Still no luck with Slughorn, then,
I take it?
슬러그혼하곤
운 좀 있었어?
Luck.
행운!
That's it. All I need's a bit of luck.
내게 필요한 건
바로 행운이야
Well, how do you feel?
기분 어때?
Excellent.
최고야
Really excellent.
진짜 최고야
Remember...
명심해
...Slughorn usually eats early...
슬러그혼은 일찍 저녁 먹고
...takes a walk,
and then returns to his office.
산책한 후에 방으로 돌아가
Right.
알았어
- I'm going down to Hagrid's.
- What?
- 해그리드한테 갈래
- 뭐?
No, Harry, you've got to go
and speak to Slughorn.
안돼, 슬러그혼을 만나야지
- We have a plan.
- I know...
- 계획대로 해
- 그건 알지만
...but I've got a
good feeling about Hagrid's.
해그리드한테
가야 될 거 같아
I feel it's the place to be tonight.
Do you know what I mean?
거기 가야만 된다구
말뜻 알겠어?
- No.
- Well, trust me, I know what I'm doing.
- 아니
- 날 믿어
Or Felix does.
아님 행운의 물약을!
Hi!
안녕!
Merlin's beard, Harry!
마법사 맙소사, 해리!
Sorry, sir. I should've announced myself.
Cleared my throat, coughed.
죄송해요
인기척 냈어야 했는데
You probably feared
I was Professor Sprout.
스프라우트 교수님인지
아셨죠?
Yes, I did, actually.
What makes you think that?
그래, 어떻게 알았지?
Well, just the general behavior, sir.
들킬까 봐 살금살금
The sneaking around,
the jumping when you saw me.
절 보곤
깜짝 놀라셨잖아요
Are those Tentacula leaves, sir?
They're very valuable, aren't they?
텐타큘라 잎이네요
아주 비싸다죠?
Ten Galleons a leaf to the right buyer.
잎 하나에 10갈레온이야
Not that I'm familiar with any such
transactions, but one does hear rumors.
암시장에서 사 본 적 없지만
소문 들었지
My own interests
are purely academic, of course.
난 학문적인 용도로만
사용해
Personally, these plants
always kind of freaked me out.
이 식물들만 보면
소름이 끼쳐요
How did you get out of the castle, Harry?
성에서 어떻게 나왔어?
Through the front door, sir.
정문으로요
I'm off to Hagrid's.
He's a very dear friend...
해그리드한테 가요
좋은 친구거든요
...and I fancied paying him a visit.
So if you don't mind,
I will be going now.
그럼 전 이만!
Harry!
해리!
- Sir?
- It's nearly nightfall.
- 교수님!
- 곧 해가 지는데
Surely you realize I can't allow you
to go roaming the grounds by yourself.
혼자 돌아다니게
놔둘 순 없어
Well, then, by all means, come along, sir.
그럼 같이 가세요
Harry, I must insist
you accompany me...
해리! 당장 나랑
성으로 돌아가자
...back to the castle immediately!
That would be counterproductive, sir.
그럼 헛수고가 돼요
And what makes you say that?
무슨 소리야?
No idea.
몰라요
Horace.
호레이스
Merlin's beard.
Is that an actual Acromantula?
마법사 맙소사!
진짜 애크로맨투라야?
A dead one, I think, sir.
죽은 거 같네요
Good God.
맙소사
Dear fellow,
however did you manage to kill it?
이보게, 어떻게 죽인 거야?
Kill it? Me oldest friend, he was.
죽이다뇨!
내 친한 친구였어요
- I'm so sorry, I didn't...
- Don't worry yourself, you're not alone.
- 난 그냥…
- 괜찮아요, 다들 그런걸요
Seriously misunderstood creatures,
spiders are.
착한 동물인데
모두가 겁내요
It's the eyes, I reckon.
They unnerve some folk.
아마 눈 때문에
무섭나 봐요
Not to mention the pincers.
집게발도!
Yeah, I reckon that too.
그래, 그것도
Hagrid, the last thing
I wish to be is indelicate...
해그리드
추모 분위기 깨긴 싫지만
...but Acromantular venom
is uncommonly rare.
애크로맨투라 독은
굉장히 귀해
Would you allow me
to extract a vial or two?
좀 뽑아도 되겠나?
Purely for academic purposes,
you understand.
학문적으로 사용하려구
Well, I don't suppose it's going
to do him much good now, is it?
죽었으니까
독은 필요 없겠죠
My thoughts exactly.
내 말이!
Always have a ampoule or two about
my person for just such occasions as this.
이런 상황에 대비해
항상 작은 병을 휴대하지
Old Potions Master's habit, you know.
마법약 교수의 직업병이야
I wish you could've seen him
in his prime.
한창 때 모습을
봤어야 하는데
Magnificent, he was. Just magnificent.
눈부셨어요
눈이 부셨다구요!
Oh, dear.
- Would you like me to say a few words?
- Yes.
- 추도사 해줄까?
- 네
He had a family, I trust?
가족이 있겠지?
Oh, yeah.
네
Farewell...
잘 가게
Aragog.
아라고그
Farewell, Aragog...
잘 가게, 아라고그
...king of the arachnids.
거미족의 왕이여
Your body will decay...
몸은 비록 썩어 없어지지만
...but your spirit lingers on.
영혼은 우리 곁에
영원할지니
And your human friends find solace
in the loss they have sustained.
인간 친구들이
슬픔을 이겨 내길…
영원한 안식 속에
그를 눕히니
마법의 지팡이가
반으로 부러졌네
I had him from an egg, you know.
Tiny little thing he was when he hatched.
막 알 깨고 나왔을 땐
No bigger than a Pekinese.
A Pekinese, mind you.
애완견 페키니즈보다
훨씬 작았어요
How sweet. I once had a fish. Francis.
He was very dear to me.
난 프란시스란
물고기 키웠었는데
One afternoon I came downstairs,
and he'd vanished.
하루는 아래층에 내려와 보니
연기처럼 사라지고 없었어
Poof.
펑
- That's very odd, isn't it?
- It is, isn't it?
- 참 별일이네요
- 그렇지?
But that's life, I suppose.
하지만 바로 그런 게
인생이야
You go along and then suddenly, poof!
순탄하다 싶다가도
갑자기… 펑
- Poof.
펑
It was a student who gave me Francis.
그 물고기
학생한테 선물 받았어
One spring afternoon
I discovered a bowl on my desk...
봄이었는데 책상에
어항이 놓여 있더군
...with just a few inches
of clear water in it.
물이 약간 차 있고
And floating on the surface
was a flower petal.
꽃잎 하나가 떠 있었지
As I watched, it sank.
그게 가라앉더니
Just before it reached the bottom...
바닥에 닿기 직전
...it transformed...
아주 작은 물고기로
...into a wee fish.
변했어
It was beautiful magic.
아름다운 마법이었지
Wondrous to behold.
황홀한 광경이었어
The flower petal had come from a lily.
꽃잎은 릴리, 백합이었단다
Your mother.
네 엄마 말이다
The day I came downstairs...
아래층으로 내려온 날
...the day the bowl was empty...
어항의 물이 사라진 날
...was the day your mother...
네 엄마가…
I know why you're here.
네가 뭘 원하는지 안다
But I can't help you.
하지만 못 도와줘
It would ruin me.
그랬다간 난 끝장이야
Do you know why I survived, professor?
제가 살아남은 이유
아세요?
The night I got this?
이 흉터 생긴 날?
Because of her.
엄마 덕분이에요
Because she sacrificed herself.
절 위해 희생하셨죠
Because she refused to step aside.
피하지 않으셨어요
Because her love was more powerful
than Voldemort.
엄마 사랑이
볼드모트보다 강했죠
- Don't say his name.
- I'm not afraid of the name, professor.
- 그 이름 말하지 마
- 전 두렵지 않아요
I'm going to tell you something.
말할 게 있어요
Something others have only guessed at.
딴 사람들은
소문으로만 아는 거죠
It's true.
사실이에요
I am the Chosen One.
제가 선택받은 자죠
Only I can destroy him,
but in order to do so...
그를 쓰러뜨리자면
...I need to know what Tom Riddle
asked you years ago in your office...
그때 톰 리들과
어떤 대화 했는지
...and I need to know what you told him.
꼭 알아야 돼요
Be brave, professor.
용기를 내세요, 교수님
Be brave like my mother.
우리 엄마처럼요
Otherwise, you disgrace her.
그렇지 않음 엄마의 명예를
Otherwise, she died for nothing.
엄마 죽음을
헛되게 하는 거예요
Otherwise, the bowl
will remain empty forever.
어항의 물은
영원히 마를 거구요
Please, don't think badly of me
when you see it.
이걸 보고
날 나쁘게 생각 마라
You've no idea what he was like,
even then.
어떤 녀석이었는지
넌 상상도 못 해
I was in the library the other night...
도서관에 갔다가
...in the Restricted Section...
금서 구역에서
...and I read something rather odd
about a bit of rare magic.
이상한 마법에 관한
책을 읽었어요
It's called, as I understand it...
그 마법의 이름은
...a Horcrux.
호크룩스예요
- I beg your pardon?
- Horcrux.
- 뭐라구?
- 호크룩스
I came across the term while reading...
책에서 우연히 봤는데
...and I didn't fully understand it.
이해가 안 돼서요
I'm not sure what you
were reading, Tom...
뭘 읽었는진 모르지만
그건 어둠의 마법이야
...but this is very dark stuff,
very dark indeed.
Which is...
그러니까
...why I came to you.
교수님을 찾아온 거죠
A Horcrux is an object in which a person
has concealed part of their soul.
호크룩스는 영혼의 일부를
숨기는 물건을 뜻한다
But I don't understand
how that works, sir.
어떤 원리인지
이해가 안 돼요
One splits one's soul and hides
part of it in an object.
영혼을 조각내서
감추는 거야
By doing so, you're protected, should
you be attacked and your body destroyed.
그럼 공격을 받아도
안전하거든
Protected?
어떻게요?
That part of your soul
that is hidden lives on.
몸이 죽어도
영혼은 살아 있으니
In other words, you cannot die.
불멸의 삶을 사는 거지
And how does one split his soul, sir?
영혼을 어떻게 조각내죠?
I think you already know
the answer to that, Tom.
이미 알고 있잖아, 톰
Murder.
살인!
Yes.
그래
Killing rips the soul apart.
It is a violation against nature.
살인을 하면 영혼이 타락해
조각이 나지
Can you only split the soul
once? For instance, isn't seven...?
한 번만 가능해요?
7번은?
Seven?
7번?
Merlin's beard, Tom. Isn't it bad enough
to consider killing one person?
맙소사, 톰
어떻게 그런 생각을!
To rip the soul into seven pieces...
영혼을 7조각으로
나누면…
This is all hypothetical, isn't it, Tom?
All academic?
그냥 하는 소리지?
공부 목적으로?
Of course, sir.
그럼요, 교수님
It'll be our little secret.
우리 대화는 비밀로 할게요
Sir.
교수님
This is beyond anything I imagined.
내가 상상한 것 이상이야
You mean to say he succeeded, sir,
in making a Horcrux?
그가 호크룩스를
성공한 건가요?
Oh, yes, he succeeded, all right.
And not just once.
그래, 성공했지
한 번뿐만이 아냐
What are they exactly?
뭘로요?
Could be anything.
Most commonplace of objects.
우리 주변의 물건
뭐든지 가능해
A ring, for example.
반지나
Or a book.
책
- Tom Riddle's diary.
- It's a Horcrux, yes.
- 톰 리들의 일기장!
- 호크룩스다
Four years ago, when you saved
Ginny's life...
4년 전
네가 비밀의 방에서
...in the Chamber of Secrets,
you brought me this.
지니 구하고 가져왔을 때
I knew this was
a different kind of magic.
다른 마법인 걸 알았다
Very dark, very powerful. But until tonight
I had no idea just how powerful.
어둡고 강력했지
이 정도인진 몰랐지만…
- The ring?
- Belonged to Voldemort's mother.
- 반지는요?
- 볼드모트 어머니 거야
Difficult to find.
Even more difficult to destroy.
찾기도 힘들지만
파괴하긴 더 힘들어
But if you could find them all,
if you did destroy each Horcrux...
호크룩스를
전부 찾아내 파괴하면…
One destroys Voldemort.
볼드모트가 죽게 되지
But how would you find them?
They could be hidden anywhere.
하지만 어디 숨겨진지
모르잖아요
True. But magic, especially dark magic...
그래, 허나 어둠의 마법은…
...leaves traces.
흔적을 남긴다
It's where you've been going,
isn't it, sir?
여행 가신다고 한 게
그걸 찾으러?
- When you leave the school?
- Yes.
그래
And I think perhaps
I may have found another.
세 번째 호크룩스는
찾은 거 같다
But this time,
I cannot hope to destroy it alone.
하지만 이번엔
나 혼자 파괴 못 해
Once again,
I must ask too much of you, Harry.
또 네 도움을
받아야겠구나, 해리
Have you ever considered
that you ask too much...
이젠 너무 당연하다는 듯이
...that you take too much for granted?
말씀하시는군요
Has it ever crossed your brilliant mind
that I don't want to do this anymore?
교수님 뜻대로
하기로 했지만
그것만은
하고 싶지 않다면요?
Whether it has or hasn't is irrelevant.
그러기엔 너무 늦었네
I will not negotiate with you, Severus.
You agreed. Nothing more to discuss.
약속대로 해주게, 스네이프
얘기 끝내지
Oh, Harry.
해리
You need a shave, my friend.
면도해야겠구나
You know, at times,
I forget how much you've grown.
이젠 너도 어른인 걸
자꾸 잊는다
At times, I still see the small boy
from the cupboard.
내 눈엔 아직도
벽장 안에 사는 꼬마야
Forgive my mawkishness, Harry.
이해해 주렴
I'm an old man.
나도 이젠 늙었어
You still look the same to me, sir.
예전과 똑같으세요
Just like your mother,
you're unfailingly kind.
넌 엄마를 닮았어
배려심이 깊지
A trait people never fail to undervalue,
I'm afraid.
사람들은 그런 점을
너무나 당연시해
The place to which we journey tonight
is extremely dangerous.
오늘 밤 가는 곳은
아주 위험하지만
I promised you could accompany me,
and I stand by that promise.
데려간다고 했으니
약속을 지켜야겠지
But there is one condition:
조건이 있다
You must obey every command
I give you, without question.
내 말에 무조건
따라야 돼
Yes, sir.
네
You do understand what I'm saying?
무슨 말인지 알지?
Should I tell you to hide, you hide.
내가 숨으라면 숨고
Should I tell you to run, you run.
도망치라면 도망쳐
Should I tell you to abandon me
and save yourself, you must do so.
날 버리고 가라면
그렇게 해야 된다
Your word, Harry.
약속해라
My word.
약속해요
Take my arm.
내 팔을 잡아
Sir, I thought you couldn't
Apparate within Hogwarts.
호그와트 안에선
순간 이동 금지잖아요
Well, being me has its privileges.
난 교장이야, 못할 게 없지
This is the place.
여기다
Oh, yes.
그래
This place has known magic.
마법이 쓰인 흔적이 있어
- Sir!
- In order to gain passage...
- 교수님!
- 들어가려면 대가를 치러야 돼
...payment must be made.
Payment intended
to weaken any intruder.
침입자의 힘을
약화시키는 거지
- You should've let me, sir.
- No, Harry.
- 절 시키시지…
- 아니다
Your blood's much more precious
than mine.
네 피는 내 피보다
더 귀중해
Voldemort will not have made it easy
to discover his hiding place.
쉽게 찾도록
놔두진 않았을 거다
He will have put certain defenses
in position.
방어 수단을 세워 놨겠지
Careful.
조심해
There it is.
저기 있다
The only question is,
how do we get there?
건너가는 게 문제군
If you would, Harry.
당겨라
Do you think the Horcrux is in there, sir?
호크룩스가
이 안에 있을까요?
Oh, yes.
그래
It has to be drunk.
다 마셔야 돼
All of it has to be drunk.
한 방울도 남김없이
You remember the conditions on which
I brought you with me?
널 데려온 조건 기억하지?
This potion might paralyze me.
마시면
내 몸이 마비될 거다
Might make me forget why I'm here.
여길 온 이유도 잊겠지
Might cause me so much pain
that I beg for relief.
고통을 못 참고 애원해도
You are not to indulge these requests.
그냥 무시해라
It's your job, Harry, to make sure
I keep drinking this potion.
내가 전부 마시게 해
Even if you have to force it
down my throat.
억지로라도 먹여
- Understood?
- Why can't I drink it, sir?
- 알았니?
- 제가 마실게요
Because I am much older, much cleverer,
and much less valuable.
난 늙었고
넌 나보다 중요한 존재야
Your good health, Harry.
건강하길 비마
Professor.
교수님!
Professor!
Harry.
Professor, can you hear me?
교수님? 제 말 들리세요?
Professor.
교수님!
No. Don't.
싫어
You have to keep drinking,
like you said. Remember?
전부 마셔야 돼요
- Stop.
- It will stop. It will stop...
- 그만
- 조금만 더 마시면 돼요
...but only if you keep drinking.
- Please, don't make me.
제발! 마시기 싫어!
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Please.
- 죄송해요
- 제발
- Kill me. Kill me!
- No!
- 날 죽여! 죽여줘!
- 안돼요!
It's my fault.
내 잘못이야
It's all my fault.
다 내 잘못이야
It's my fault.
내 잘못이야
Just one more, sir.
One more, and then I promise...
한 모금만 더요
이것만 마시면
...I promise I'll do what you say.
시키는 대로 할게요
- I promise.
- No.
- 약속해요
- 싫어
Please.
제발!
Harry.
해리
Water.
물을 줘
물…
Water.
물!
You did it, sir.
해내셨어요
Look.
보세요
Harry.
해리
Water.
물…
Aguamenti.
아쿠아멘티!
Water.
물…
Lumos.
루모스
Lumos Maxima!
루모스 맥시마!
Harry.
해리
스투페파이!
Sectumsempra!
섹튬셈프라!
Harry.
해리
인카서러스!
스투페파이!
- Stupefy!
- Harry.
Harry.
해리!
Partis Temporus!
파르티스 템포러스!
Go to your houses. No dawdling.
기숙사로 돌아가
꾸물대지 말고!
We need to get you to the hospital
wing, sir, to Madam Pomfrey.
병동에 가서
치료받으셔야 돼요
No.
아니다
Severus. Severus is who I need.
스네이프, 그가 필요해
Wake him. Tell him what happened.
깨워서 다 말해 줘
Speak to no one else.
오직 그에게만!
Severus, Harry.
스네이프한테 가
Hide yourself below, Harry.
밑에 숨어라, 해리
Don't speak or be seen by anybody
without my permission.
말을 하거나 들키면 안 돼
Whatever happens,
it's imperative you stay below.
무슨 일이 벌어져도
절대 올라오지 마라
Harry, do as I say.
시키는 대로 해
Trust me.
날 믿으렴
날 믿어
Good evening, Draco.
어서 와라, 드레이코
What brings you here
on this fine spring evening?
이 밤중에 무슨 일로 왔지?
Who else is here? I heard you talking.
누구랑 말한 거죠?
I often talk aloud to
myself. I find it extraordinarily useful.
난 혼잣말을 잘해
생각할 때 도움되지
Have you been whispering
to yourself, Draco?
네 선택이 후회되니?
Draco...
드레이코
...you are no assassin.
- How do you know what I am?
- 넌 살인자가 아냐
- 당신이 뭘 알아?
I've done things that would shock you.
난 끔찍한 짓을 했어!
Like cursing Katie Bell and hoping that in
return she'd bear a cursed necklace to me?
케이티에게 마법 걸어
내게 목걸이 주려 한 거?
Replacing a bottle of mead
with one laced with poison?
아니면 벌꿀 술에
독을 탄 거?
Forgive me, Draco.
미안하다만
I cannot help feeling these actions
are so weak...
날 진짜 죽이려 했다면
...your heart can't really
have been in them.
더 확실한 방법을 썼겠지
He trusts me. I was chosen.
그분은 날 믿어!
난 선택받았어!
Then I shall make it easy for you.
그럼 할 수 없군
Expelliarmus!
엑스펠리아르무스!
Very good. Very good.
훌륭해, 아주 훌륭해
You're not alone.
혼자가 아니구나
There are others.
그들이…
How?
어떻게?
The vanishing cabinet
in the Room of Requirement.
필요의 방에 있는
사라지는 캐비닛
- I've been mending it.
- Let me guess.
내가 고쳤어
다른 곳에
똑같은 캐비닛이 있군
It has a sister. A twin.
In Borgin and Burkes.
They form a passage.
보진과 버크 가게
Ingenious.
영리해
Draco...
드레이코
...years ago, I knew a boy
who made all the wrong choices.
예전에 잘못된 선택을 한
꼬마를 알았다
- Please let me help you.
- I don't want your help!
- 내가 도와주마
- 당신 도움 필요 없어!
Don't you understand? I have to do this.
모르겠어?
이건 내 운명이야
I have to kill you.
당신을 죽여야 돼
Or he's gonna kill me.
아님 내가 죽어
Well, look what we have here.
이게 누구신가
Well done, Draco.
잘했다, 드레이코
Good evening, Bellatrix.
반갑군, 벨라트릭스
I think introductions
are in order, don't you?
자네 친구들 소개해 줘야지?
Love to, Albus, but I'm afraid
we're all on a bit of a tight schedule.
마음은 굴뚝 같지만
그럴 시간이 없어서
Do it.
해치워!
He doesn't have the stomach,
just like his father.
죽일 배짱이 없어
지 애비처럼!
Let me finish him in my own way.
내가 해치울게
No! The Dark Lord was clear,
the boy is to do it.
안돼! 어둠의 마왕께서
꼬마한테 시켰어
This is your moment. Do it.
지금이 기회야, 해치워 버려
Go on, Draco.
어서, 드레이코
Now!
당장!
No.
안돼
Severus.
스네이프
Please.
부탁하네
Avada Kedavra.
아바다 케다브라!
Yeah!
Hagrid! Hello?
해그리드! 집에 있나?
Snape! He trusted you!
교수님은 당신을 믿었어!
Go on.
먼저 가
Incarcerous.
인카서러스!
Fight back! You coward, fight back!
싸워, 이 겁쟁이! 덤벼!
No! He belongs to the Dark Lord.
안돼!
마왕님께서 죽여야 한다
Sectumsempra!
섹튬셈프라!
You dare use my own spells
against me, Potter?
감히 내가 만든 주문을
나한테 사용해?
Yes.
그래
I'm the Half-Blood Prince.
내가 혼혈 왕자다
McGONAGALL:
Potter...
포터
...in light of what has happened...
이번 일에 대해서
...if you should have the need
to talk to someone...
얘기할 사람이
필요하다면…
You should know,
Professor Dumbledore...
너도 알 거야
덤블도어 교수님은
...you meant a great deal to him.
널 무척 아끼셨다
Do you think he would've done it?
진짜 죽였을까?
Draco?
드레이코가?
No.
아니
No, he was lowering his wand.
녀석은 지팡이를
내리고 있었어
In the end, it was Snape.
스네이프였어
It was always Snape.
스네이프가 죽였고
And I did nothing.
난 막지 못했어
It's fake.
가짜야
Open it.
열어 봐
"To the Dark Lord. I know I will be dead
long before you read this...
"어둠의 마왕에게"
"이걸 읽을 때면
난 세상에 없겠지"
...but I want you to know that it was I
who discovered your secret.
"네 비밀을 밝혀낸 건
나였다"
I have stolen the real Horcrux and intend
to destroy it as soon as I can.
"진짜 호크룩스를
훔친 것도 나였지"
I face death in the hope that
when you meet your match...
"네가 진정한 적수를 만나
죽게 된다면"
...you will be mortal once more.
"내 목숨도 아깝지 않다"
R.A.B."
"R.A.B."
R.A.B.
R.A.B.?
Don't know.
누군지 몰라
But whoever they are,
they have the real Horcrux.
진짜 호크룩스를 가진
사람이겠지
Which means it was all a waste.
교수님만 헛되이
All of it.
돌아가셨어
Ron's okay with it, you know.
론은 괜찮대
You and Ginny.
너랑 지니
But if I were you, when he's around,
I'd keep the snogging to a minimum.
그치만 론 앞에선
키스하지 마
I'm not coming back, Hermione.
학교를 떠날 거야
I've got to finish
whatever Dumbledore started.
덤블도어가 시작한 일을
끝내겠어
And I don't know where that'll lead me...
어디로 가게 될진
모르겠지만
...but I'll let you and Ron know
where I am when I can.
너하고 론한텐 꼭 연락할게
I've always admired your courage, Harry.
네 용기가 부러워
But sometimes, you can be really thick.
그치만 가끔은
너무 바보 같아
You don't really think
you're going to be able...
혼자 호크룩스를
다 찾을 수 있을 거 같아?
...to find all those Horcruxes
by yourself, do you?
You need us, Harry.
너한텐 우리가 필요해
I never realized
how beautiful this place was.
여기가 이렇게
아름다운지 몰랐어
해리 포터와 혼혈 왕자